

Kelvin Mijaya

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING MANAGER

Contact

- Springhill Terrace Residence, Kemayoran, Jakarta Utara
- kelvinmijaya@gmail.com
- (62) 812 8833 3592
- in @kelvinmijaya

Skills

Technical

Management

Communication

Leadership

About

Learning to develop is a life-changing experience. Whether I'm focusing on Website or UX, it will be exhilarating. Software development is a mentorship-driven industry and I'm enjoying it. In the end, the best I can offer is my experience.

Education History

Computer Science

2010 - 2014

BINUS University

• School of Information System

Work Experience

Tokopedia

Jan 2017 - Dec 2023

Software Engineering Manager

- Plan and execute long-term strategies that benefit the team and the product
- Foster technical decision-making on the team
- Discern engineering metrics and seek areas of improvement
- Improve processes to make frontend team more effective

OVO Finansial (Taralite)

Nov 2015 - Jan 2017

UI/UX & Frontend Lead

- Developing UX for User & Business needs
- User Testing
- Wireframes & User Interface
- Front-end Dev (ReactJS)

Bounche

Oct 2014 - Sep 2015

Frontend Web Developer

- Develop Website Template
- UX
- Custom JS Script